You're going to die, abandoned and waiting.
Four days. August 15th.
The world itself has decided that you will die.
It's inevitable,
but I won't let it happen.
I'll fight the world,
and I will save Mayuri!
The coin locker...
in front of the Daibiru.
The IBN 5100...
Even the billions of heartbeats in the world
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
are nothing to you but insignificant
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Whether we’re trapped in the past or lamenting over the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
predetermination does not allow even the slightest mistake
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The infinite dreams and futures before us
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are but vain privileges allowed to us
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finitude is what both clock hands show
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
toward a cruel destiny and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
So now I cross worldlines every second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
because I want to protect that smile of yours
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And so, a time loop without sadness will once again
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
engulf me, the lone observer
Finalize
Apoptosis
Okabe, what's wrong?
Okay! This will...
Stop!
The IBN 5100 is in a coin locker.
Moeka told me
it hasn't been recovered yet.
So?
What else?
I'll break the locker open with this!
Calm down.
Remember.
Remember what?!
Everything that's happened.
Despite all the D-Mails you've undone,
you haven't recovered the IBN 5100.
Most likely, it'll be impossible until you get back
to the original worldline.
And for that to happen, you have to do things in order.
It's so close.
But now, we have a clue.
Kiryu Moeka will do whatever this FB says, right?
And FB's the leader, right?
Then...
If I stake out the IBN 5100, maybe I'll see her.
What are you doing here?
I want to see FB too.
Didn't you want to avoid seeing her
because she'd hate you or something?
I want to know the truth.
What good will it do you?
I don't know.
Did you think I'd work with you?
Well, I guess I can talk to you.
What's wrong?
N-Nothing.
You're with Kiryu Moeka?
Why?
She's...
That's just how it worked out.
If something happens, I'll tell you.
Hey, wait!
Geez...
Was that Okarin?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
I feel like, lately, Okarin and I haven't talked at all.
Big Sis!
Nae!
Hi there, Miss Assistant!
It's Big Sis Kurisu.
Hi there.
Sorry about yesterday.
Tell Okabe his rent's going up 5,000 yen.
I-I will.
Actually, I haven't seen him today.
Did he get sick or something?
Although, they say idiots don't get sick.
I think he's looking for stuff to use in his experiments.
Experiments, huh?
What a lucky guy.
He's a student with his own damn room,
has friends like you guys,
and can do whatever he wants.
He really is lucky.
But...
Daddy, if we don't hurry, we'll miss the clearance sale!
Right! Let's go, Nae!
Bye-bye, big sisters!
Bye-bye!
What do you want for dinner?
Um...
A message from FB?
Can I see it?
"I think M4 was right."
I think M4 was right.
To be honest, no one works as hard as M4.
"To be honest, no one works as hard as M4."
M4?
That's the code name FB gave me.
Only FB and I know it.
It's a secret.
"That's true."
"You may be bad at social interactions, M4,
but that's part of what makes you you."
A mom, huh?
That's it,
the IBN 5100!
Then is he FB?
No.
FB is a woman.
I know him!
Damn it!
What's wrong?
I'll explain later.
Mister Braun?
So, have you driven since you got your license?
No.
Please drive safely.
Have you ever seen him before?
No.
What does this mean?
Four days. August 15th.
The world itself has decided that you will die.
It's inevitable.
It's on a plane to France,
SERN's country of origin.
We never saw any women who could've been FB.
At least give me a damn phone call!
I was busy.
It's not about me,
but...
Mayuri...
Come to think of it,
I think it's been a long time since we last spoke.
She said the same thing.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
We'll have to ask him directly.
Ask him?
He's someone we know very well.
What brings you here so early?
Well, come in.
So, what do you want?
Did you come to pay the extra 6,000 yen I added to your rent?
Come on now. You're supposed to say,
"That's 1,000 more yen than you said!"
There's something I'd like to ask you.
What's with the formality?
You know someone named FB, don't you?
We saw it all,
including the IBN 5100 being taken from here.
We don't care about you.
We just want to see FB.
Please tell me where she is.
You sold us out, M4.
That's the code name FB gave me.
Only FB and I know it.
Don't tell me—
What do you mean?
Ever heard of Ferdinand Braun?
The Nobel laureate who invented the Braun tube.
That's the guy.
And what are his initials?
FB.
Then you're...
That can't be true!
Do you just follow blindly and avoid reality?
Nae is asleep.
Let's go somewhere else.
This town keeps changing.
Are you really FB?
Yes.
But those messages...
I wrote them all.
Why did I write like a woman?
To trick you.
Bu—
You weren't the only one.
I message others too,
all under the guise of whomever they needed the most.
Of course, people like you are the easiest to trick, which helps.
Why break off contact with her?
The second she found the IBN 5100, I didn't need her anymore,
so I cut off contact.
We collect members through text messages.
People like that are the easiest to deal with
and the easiest to get rid of when we're done.
They don't belong anywhere.
I can't believe you're SERN's dog.
Dog?
Suzuha... Hashida Suzu
didn't take care of you for that!
How do you know about Suzu?
Suzu has nothing to do with this.
Nothing at all!
But...
What do you know?!
Ever sleep in a sewer in the middle of winter?
I was still a kid.
The concrete was so cold
that it seeped into your bones.
I didn't eat for three or four days at a time.
And when I laid down,
they came.
Rats. They thought I was dead and came to eat me.
But then, I saw a thread descend,
as thin as a spider's.
I had no choice but to climb it.
Even if, by the top,
I'd end up with dirty hands,
I kept climbing the thread.
Before I knew it, I was a marionette.
I couldn't escape.
The puppets who do escape the thread,
those traitors die.
Well, once you complete your mission, you also die.
You called me a dog, didn't you?
I'm worse than a dog.
I'm cattle.
I've thought of running before,
but I have someone I care about now.
I don't want to get her involved,
but failure isn't an option.
If you run, they go after your family.
I failed too,
but Nae won't know anything...
as long as I die.
Wait—
O-Okabe...
Okabe...
I-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
O-Okabe, his phone!
The D-Mail!
Okabe!
Stop searching for the IBN 5100, and return to standby.
Do not act under any circumstances.
Moeka...
Shining Finger
(No Subject)
I won't need the IBN 5100 for a while.
Moeka
You don't need it?
Shining Finger
(No Subject)
My boss said to stop looking for it.
Moeka
Yes, this is Urushibara.
Kyouma—
What? An IBN 5100?
Yes.
It's here!
Daru!
Hashida's not here.
He said he was going to ComiMa.
Please,
hear my request!
I see.
To save Mayuri,
we need to get out of this Alpha worldline
and return to the worldline where you didn't sent the first D-Mail,
the Beta worldline.
For that to happen, we have to erase the information from SERN's database.
Mayushi dies, and Miss Amane is my daughter from the future.
If that's all bullshit, I think Okarin could become quite the writer.
I wish that was true.
You believe it, Miss Makise?
For a hypothesis,
if feasible, I'd prefer some reliable, objective data,
but I guess that's impossible.
The time leap machine you made worked perfectly.
D-Did it?
O-Of course it did!
And...
What?
Nothing.
Wh-What?
I said nothing.
It's connected.
I need to know the settings, but I can start in ten minutes.
I'm counting on you, supah hakah.
Super hacker.
The first D-Mail, huh?
That's the one where I was stabbed, right?
Did you try to feel me up or something?
By undoing all the D-Mails, I'd return to the original worldline:
the worldline in which SERN doesn't establish a dystopia
and the worldline in which Mayuri doesn't die.
However, in that worldline...
Makise Kurisu...
dies.
kisei sareta shikai mujihi naru
With my field of view restricted
juuni no shihai nogarerarenai
I cannot escape the merciless control of the twelve
ansoku no asu wo negatta
While wishing for a tomorrow of repose
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
I headed for the sacred event horizon in my hand
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
Pledges are imprisoned, and false evidences are showing their outline
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
This world of life blindly lets the time pass by
habatake butterfly
Spread your wings
kiseki no butterfly
butterfly of miracles
anata he sasagu
I dedicate it to you
namida no butterfly
Oh butterfly of tears
mabushii butterfly
butterfly of radiance
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
everything will now be rewritten